Guide to the Amos Niven Wilder and Wilder Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Janet Wilder Dakin Papers, 1816–1994; Series VI
  - Thornton Wilder materials, 1896–1993
    - Thornton Wilder correspondence addressed to Miriam Beer Hoffmann Lens transcriptions, 1981 (Box 147, Folder 2067)
      Includes photocopies of a program assembled by Franz Link.
    - Thornton Wilder German memorial materials, 1976 (Box 147, Folder 2068)
      Includes a list of Thornton Wilder's correspondence, clippings, correspondence, and notes.
    - Bert correspondence, 1953 (Box 148, Folder 2069)
    - Undated correspondence (Box 394, Folder 5221)
      Valentines addressed to "Kate", potentially belonging to Elizabeth Lewis Niven.
    - The Concord Players' Our Town photographs, 1985 (Box 148, Folder 2070)
    - Schiller-Theater Wekstatt progam, 1962–1963 (Box 148, Folder 2071)
    - Theater programs and writing publications, 1896–1950 (Box 148, Folder 2072-2073)
    - Wilder, Thornton materials, undated (Box 148, Folder 2074)
    - 100 Jahre S. Fischer, 1986 (Box 148, Folder 2075)
      The correspondence includes no last name.
    - Poesie by Robert Lowell, edited by Rolando Anzilotti, 1955 (Box 148, Folder 2076)
      Also includes a map of the city of Carmel -by-the Sea, California included in oversize box.
    - Thornton Niven Wilder memorial program, 1976 (Box 148, Folder 2077)
    - Goldstein, Malcolm book notes, undated (Box 148, Folder 2078)
    - Thornton Wilder: An Intimate Portrait reviews, 1975 (Box 148, Folder 2079)
      Includes issues of American Poetry Magazine, S4N, The Christian Century, and playbills from The Seagull, How Beautiful with Shoes, The Comic Artist, and The Buccaneer.
    - Wilder, Thornton and Channing, Carol document, 1977 (Box 148, Folder 2080)
      Includes Isabel's writing on Hello Dolly, a list of The Skin of Our Teeth publications abroad, and text samples for The Bridge of San Luis Rey.
    - Who's Who materials, 1971–1976 (Box 148, Folder 2081)
      Also includes material for Men of Achievement and an issue of Current Biography.
    - Brown, Arvin correspondence, 1984–1987 (Box 148, Folder 2082)
      Correspondence from the artistic director of the Long Wharf Theatre.
    - Theatre correspondence, 1983–1985 (Box 148, Folder 2083)
    - Receipts, furniture and house repairs, 1979–1988 (Box 148, Folder 2084)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1960–1988 (Box 148, Folder 2085)
    - Photocopied recipes, undated (Box 148, Folder 2086)
    - Wilder, Thornton photographs, circa 1957-1978 (Box 148, Folder 2087-2088)
      Includes reprints and photographs of the Wilder family and Thornton Wilder.
    - Wilder, Thornton Memorial Lecture at the German School, 1977–1979 (Box 148, Folder 2089-2090)
    - German School correspondence, 1976–1978 (Box 148, Folder 2091)
    - General German correspondence, 1969–1976 (Box 148, Folder 2092)
    - MacDowell Colony correspondence, clippings, and brochures, 1973–1992 (Box 149, Folder 2093)
    - Wilder, Amos Parker fragment, undated (Box 149, Folder 2094)
      Includes a piece focusing on his family's life.
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1943–1989 (Box 149, Folder 2095-2097)
      Also includes notes, a hotel bill, and a guest pass for the American Theater Wing Stage Door Canteen. Also includes correspondence from Ruth Gordon, Alfred Swan, and letters addressed to Richard Goldstone.
    - Thornton Niven Wilder Award correspondence, 1992 (Box 149, Folder 2098)
      A typescript of a letter addressed to Mabel Dodge dated January 17, 1937
    - Yale in China materials, 1976–1983 (Box 149, Folder 2099)
      Includes clippings, correspondence, and writings.
    - Thornton Wilder Journals clippings and correspondence, 1985 (Box 149, Folder 2100-2101)
    - Union and New Haven Trust Company financial account statement, 1967–1968 (Box 149, Folder 2102)
    - Wilder, Thornton photocopied correspondence, circa 1981 (Box 149, Folder 2103)
    - Wilder, Thornton and Beer-Hoffmann correspondence appraisal materials, 1981 (Box 149, Folder 2104)
    - Wilder, Thornton typescript correspondence, undated (Box 149, Folder 2105)
    - Photocopied list of Thornton Wilder's letters to Amy W. Wertheimer, undated (Box 149, Folder 2106)
    - Condolence correspondence addressed to Amos and Catharine Wilder, 1975–1976 (Box 149, Folder 2107-2109)
      Includes letters send to Amos after his brother's death and clippings.
    - Fridericus Berghuis' Partial Latin Translation of Lazarillo de Tormes and its Relationship to the Early Lazarillo Translations in Germany, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 2110)
    - Wilder, Thornton clippings, 1926–1986 (Box 150, Folder 2111-2117)
    - Translation, 1974 (Box 150, Folder 2118)
      Also includes receipts and some of Amos Niven Wilder's personal correspondence.
    - Photocopy radio transcript of announcement of Thornton Wilder's death, 1975 (Box 150, Folder 2119)
    - Wilder, Thornton correspondence information, 1978 (Box 150, Folder 2120)
    - Theater programs, 1977–1984 (Box 150, Folder 2121)
      Includes programs from PCPA/ Solvang Theaterfest, A Celebration of Thornton Wilder at the Circle in the Square Theatre, and the Great Lakes Shakespeare Festival.
    - Ordens Pour Le Mérite für Wissenschaften und Künste correspondence, 1966–1979 (Box 150, Folder 2122)
    - Tributes of the Presentation of the Peace Prize at Frankfurt photocopy typescript, undated (Box 150, Folder 2123)
    - Wilder, Thornton Thacher School photocopied article and correspondence, 1976 (Box 150, Folder 2124)
    - Wilder, Thornton, The Enthusiast photocopied clippings, 1983 (Box 150, Folder 2125)
    - Wilder, Wilder program, clippings, and correspondence, 1978–1979 (Box 150, Folder 2126, Box 108 (Oversize), Folder 1492)
      Includes oversized poster from Wilder, Wilder.
    - Wiseman, T.P. photocopied correspondence, 1984 (Box 150, Folder 2127)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth clippings, 1975–1983 (Box 150, Folder 2128)
    - Wilder, Thornton clippings, circa 1928 (Box 150, Folder 2129)
    - Wilder, Thornton photocopied reviews and clippings, undated (Box 150, Folder 2130-2131)
    - Carmen playbill, 1981 (Box 150, Folder 2132)
    - The New Criterion, 1985 (Box 150, Folder 2133)
    - Wilder of Our Town by Alfred W. Swan, 1981 (Box 150, Folder 2134)
    - Books and Bookmen, 1976 (Box 152, Folder 2135)
      Includes a typescript photocopy of a paper read at the Madison Literary Club.
    - Archives of American Art, 1978 (Box 152, Folder 2136)
    - The American Scholar, 1985 (Box 152, Folder 2137)
    - First name correspondence, Lillian, 1965 (Box 152, Folder 2138)
      Includes the article "Remembering Thornton Wilder" written by Elder Olson.
    - Wilder family correspondence, 1920–1943 (Box 152, Folder 2139)
    - Wixson, Douglas, 1978–1982 (Box 152, Folder 2140)
      Includes a letter from William Taft to Amos Parker Wilder.
    - Poulakos, John correspondence and "The Philosophy of the Interhuman: Thornton Wilder's The Bridge of San Luis Rey ", 1982 (Box 152, Folder 2141)
      Includes correspondence, Wixson's writings, and Studies in the Humanities.
    - The Art of Thornton Wilder review written by Richard Goldstone typescript and photocopies, circa 1965 (Box 152, Folder 2142)
    - Theatre programs and photocopied articles, 1976–1986 (Box 152, Folder 2143)
    - Review, 1937 (Box 152, Folder 2144)
    - Harrison, Gilbert correspondence and clippings, 1983- (Box 152, Folder 2145)
      A review of Wilder's work from an unknown source.
    - The Enthusiast: A Life of Thornton Wilder clippings and promotional materials, 1983 (Box 152, Folder 2146-2149)
    - Wilder, Thornton The Alcestiad clippings and reviews, 1976–1978 (Box 152, Folder 2150-2151)
      Includes a book jacket, photocopied reviews from The New Haven Register and The Smithsonian Magazine as well as other periodicals.
    - The Journals of Thornton Wilder clippings, 1985 (Box 152, Folder 2152)
    - Hello Dolly clipping and photographs, 1979–1990 (Box 152, Folder 2153)
    - Shadow of a Doubt clipping, undated (Box 152, Folder 2154)
    - Our Town, musical version, clippings and photocopy typescript fragments, 1987–1990 (Box 152, Folder 2155)
    - Our Town at the Shaftesbury Theatre brochure and clipping, circa 1991 (Box 152, Folder 2156)
    - Our Town clippings, 1987–1990 (Box 152, Folder 2157-2159, Box 413 (Broadside))
    - Our Town programs, 1987–1993 (Box 153, Folder 2160-2163)
      Includes a photograph from the Concord Players.
    - Mr. North clipping fragment, undated (Box 153, Folder 2164)
    - Movie adaptation clippings, 1968–1982 (Box 153, Folder 2165)
    - Memorial service thank you notes and speech fragment, 1976 (Box 153, Folder 2166)
    - Family photographs, circa 1951-1969 (Box 153, Folder 2167)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth programs and photocopied articles, 1975–1993 (Box 153, Folder 2168)
    - Theophilus in New York photocopied handwritten and typescript, circa 1992 (Box 153, Folder 2169)
    - Time magazine cover, 1953 (Box 153, Folder 2170)
    - The Rocket photocopied typescript with Thornton Wilder's annotations, undated (Box 153, Folder 2171)
    - Jennie Jerome typescript manuscript, circa 1975 (Box 153, Folder 2172)
    - Wilder, Wilder, Wilder program and clippings, 1993 (Box 153, Folder 2173)
      Includes a photograph signed by the cast.
    - Wilder, Thornton bust and study unveilings clippings, 1983–1986 (Box 153, Folder 2174)
    - Wilder, Thornton photocopied memorial articles, circa 1976 (Box 153, Folder 2175-2176)
    - Our Town photocopied articles, 1988 (Box 153, Folder 2177)
    - Orden Pour Le Mérite Für Wissenschaften und Künste and speech fragment, 1976 (Box 153, Folder 2178)
    - Thornton Wilder Memorial Lecture at the German School, 1976 (Box 153, Folder 2179)
    - The Turnabout Theatre photocopied clippings, undated (Box 153, Folder 2180)
    - A Celebration of Thornton Wilder at the Circle in the Square Theatre photocopied clippings and program, 1977 (Box 153, Folder 2181)
    - Great Lakes Shakespeare Festival and related clippings, 1984–1990 (Box 154, Folder 2182)
    - Literature and Religion: Thornton Wilder's The Eighth Day collected for MLA Seminar 4, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 2183)
    - The Alcestiad materials
      - Correspondence, 1977–1979 (Box 155, Folder 2204-2205)
        Also includes programs from Louise Talma's "A Memorial Tribute to Thornton Wilder".
      - Book and opera photocopied reviews and clippings, 1977–1979 (Box 155, Folder 2206-2207)
      - Correspondence, clippings, and notes, 1977–1978 (Box 155, Folder 2208)
      - Opera programs and clippings, 1976 (Box 155, Folder 2209)
        Also includes correspondence from Louise Talma.
      - Performance at St. Joseph's University, 1977–1981 (Box 155, Folder 2210)
      - Performance at the University Alumnae Dramatic Club in Toronto, 1978 (Box 155, Folder 2211)
      - Photocopied notes and clippings, 1978 (Box 155, Folder 2212)
        Correspondence with Esther Jackson from the University of Wisconsin, Madison on a project on The Alcestiad.
      - Jackson, Esther correspondence, 1983 (Box 155, Folder 2213)
      - Graduate student correspondence, 1979 (Box 155, Folder 2214)
      - Correspondence, 1977–1978 (Box 155, Folder 2215)
      - French production correspondence, 1980–1981 (Box 155, Folder 2216)
      - Missouri Repertory Theatre correspondence, 1978 (Box 155, Folder 2217)
      - Santa Maria, California production correspondence, photocopied articles, and notes, 1978 (Box 155, Folder 2218)
      - Town of Hamden, Connecticut Resolution of the Legislative Council, 1975 (Box 155, Folder 2219)
      - Congressional Record in memory of Thornton Wilder, 1975 (Box 155, Folder 2220)
        Council movement in memory of Thornton Wilder.
      - "Overland Monthly", 1911 (Box 155, Folder 2221)
      - Niven family correspondence and photographs, 1849–1923 (Box 156, Folder 2222-2223)
        Includes an article about consular representatives in China which mentions Amos P. Wilder.
      - Bessie (potentially Turpin/Niven) correspondence, undated (Box 156, Folder 2224)
        Also includes Elizabeth L. Niven's last will and testament and the Manuals of the Presbyterian Church of Greenburgh.
      - Wilder, Charlotte typescript photocopied correspondence, 1969 (Box 156, Folder 2225)
      - Wilder genealogy clippings and correspondence, 1816–1954 (Box 156, Folder 2226-2228)
        Also includes a letter from Amos Niven to Isabel.
      - Olds Seed Company annual reports, 1932-1933, 1970 (Box 156, Folder 2229)
      - Niven, Thornton MacNess clipping, undated (Box 156, Folder 2230)
        Also includes a photocopied typescript of an article entitled The Giving of Yale Men written by Amos Parker Wilder which appeared in the New Haven Journal Courier in 1927.
      - The Eighth Day handwritten fragment, undated (Box 156, Folder 2231)
      - Williams, Herschel correspondence, 1977–1985 (Box 156, Folder 2232)
        A fragment entitled "St. Kitts: Sickness" handwritten by Thornton Wilder.
      - Wilder, Isabel notes, fragments, and keys, circa 1956 (Box 156, Folder 2233)
      - The Woman of Andros photocopied handwritten fragment, undated (Box 156, Folder 2234)
      - Beulah photocopied correspondence and articles, undated (Box 156, Folder 2235)
      - "Mortality and Contemporary Literature" written by Amos N. Wilder reprinted from The Harvard Theological Review, 1965 (Box 156, Folder 2236)
      - Ordens pour le Merite fur Wissenschaften und Kunste, 1970–1976 (Box 156, Folder 2237-2239)
      - The Current Company's Pen and Pencil catalog, 1928 (Box 156, Folder 2240)
      - Wilder family correspondence accompanying photocopied Thornton Wilder correspondence, 1991–1992 (Box 156, Folder 2241)
        Letters from Tappy and Dixie Wilder addressed to Isabel Wilder along with photocopied correspondence from Thornton Wilder addressed to Robert M. Hutchins and Miss Etnyre.
      - United States Savings Bond, 1945 (Box 156, Folder 2242)
      - Photocopied Thornton Wilder correspondence fragment addressed to Mr. Weeks of The Atlantic, undated (Box 156, Folder 2243)
    - Isabel's writing related materials
      - Wilder, Isabella correspondence addressed to Amos Niven, 1915–1945 (Box 154, Folder 2184)
        Also includes letters from Isabel and Charlotte addressed to Amos Niven as well as poetry written in Isabella's hand.
      - Wilder, Amos Niven correspondence, 1975–1977 (Box 154, Folder 2185)
        Photocopied and handwritten letters addressed to Amos Niven Wilder.
      - Wilder family correspondence, 1930–1963 (Box 154, Folder 2186)
      - Wilder, Charlotte correspondence, 1917–1961 (Box 154, Folder 2187)
      - Bachelor, Clementine correspondence, 1917; undated (Box 154, Folder 2188)
      - Dakin, Janet Wilder correspondence, circa 1932- 1961 (Box 154, Folder 2189-2191)
        Also includes a letter addressed to Thornton.
      - Wilder, Catharine Kerlin correspondence, 1945 (Box 154, Folder 2192)
      - First Congregational Church correspondence, 1928 (Box 154, Folder 2193)
      - Coward telegrams, 1932 (Box 154, Folder 2194)
      - Wilder, Isabel photographs, circa 1939 (Box 154, Folder 2195)
      - Berkeley home address, undated (Box 154, Folder 2196)
        The second folder contains correspondence also addressed to Amos Parker Wilder.
      - Wilder, Isabella Niven correspondence, 1917–1946 (Box 154, Folder 2197-2199)
      - Wilder, Isabella Niven correspondence, 1917–1946 (Box 155, Folder 2200-2201)
      - Wilder, Amos Niven correspondence, 1913–1948 (Box 155, Folder 2202-2203)
  - Thornton Wilder bibliography materials, 1955–1957
    - Wilder, Thornton bibliography, undated (Box 157, Folder 2244-2246)
    - Edelstein, Jerome Melvin third party correspondence, 1955–1957 (Box 157, Folder 2247-2250)
    - Wilder, Thornton bibliography, undated (Box 157, Folder 2251-2253)
    - Wilder, Thornton bibliography, undated (Box 158, Folder 2254-2257)
  - Personal papers, 1927–1990
    - Wilder, Isabel oral history correspondence, transcripts, writings, and notes, 1981; undated (Box 158, Folder 2258-2259)
      Dorothy Ulrich Troubetzkoy conducted a series of interviews with Isabel about her childhood, family life, and Thornton Wilder's friends including Jed Harris, Richard Goldstone, Linda Simon, and Max Reinhardt.
    - "Addresse: Hotel Pension de La Famille, Vevey, La Suisse", undated (Box 158, Folder 2260)
    - Turnabout Theatre materials, 1945- circa 1985 (Box 158, Folder 2261-2262)
      Includes correspondence, ephemera, photocopied articles, and photographs.
    - Wilder, Isabel writings, undated (Box 158, Folder 2263-2264)
      Typescripts of "Crossing with the Lamb", "The Incident in Thornton's Childhood which Turned into an Experience with Far-Reaching Important Results", "The Lady Has a Past", "Foreword: Born to Read and Write", and untitled fragments.
    - The Merchant of Yonkers typescript transcript (Box 158, Folder 2265)
    - Wilder, Isabel work notes and fragments, 1965 (Box 158, Folder 2266)
      Mostly handwritten notes and typescript on the Wilder family.
    - "Pen, Paper, Shelves and Stacks" photocopied typescripts, undated (Box 159, Folder 2267)
    - Dakin, Janet Wilder correspondence, 1931–1987 (Box 159, Folder 2268-2275)
      Addressed to her mother, her father, Isabel, and her family. Also includes letters from Toby Dakin to family members as well as clippings about the Dakins.
    - Wilder, Isabel birthday cards and letters, 1950–1990 (Box 159, Folder 2276-2277)
    - The Alcestiad foreword, undated (Box 160, Folder 2278)
      Several typescript copies, some of which are annotated.
    - Typescript fragments, 1927; undated (Box 160, Folder 2279)
      Includes potential fragments from The Alcestiad foreword.
    - Writings and fragments, 1954 (Box 160, Folder 2280-2281)
      Typescript and handwritten pieces including the following titles: "My Mother's Tears", "All Seven", "My Mother's Homes", and "Thanksgiving, Lausanne".
    - "Born to Read and Write: An Outline of Thornton Wilder's Legacy to the Beinecke Library of Rare Books and Manuscripts (2 folders), undated (Box 160, Folder 2282-2283)
      The second folder includes a fragment labeled "Foreword".
    - "Ink, Paper, Shelves and Stacks" typescript and "Fortnightly" fragment, undated (Box 160, Folder 2284)
    - "Thornton Wilder and Richard Beer-Hofmann" photocopied fragments, undated (Box 160, Folder 2285)
      Photocopied correspondence from the work complied by Jeffrey B. Berlin.
    - "A Double Life", "Pen, Paper, Shelves and Stacks", and "All Seven" typescripts, undated (Box 160, Folder 2286)
    - Handwritten journal entries, 1943–1945 (Box 160, Folder 2287)
    - Toubetzkoy typescript transcripts of oral history interviews with Isabel Wilder, 1981–1982 (Box 160, Folder 2288)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1957–1994
    - Axion Research Foundation correspondence, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 2289)
    - The Century Association correspondence, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 2290)
    - Crowley, Dennis correspondence, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 2291)
    - Crowley, Stephen correspondence, 1989–1992 (Box 160, Folder 2292)
    - Williams, Michael correspondence, 1990 (Box 160, Folder 2293)
    - Academy and Institute correspondence, 1970–1976 (Box 160, Folder 2294)
      Includes correspondence from the Wisconsin Academy of Sciences, Arts and Letters, the American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, and the National Institute of Arts and Letters.
    - Wisconsin Academy review, 1993 (Box 161, Folder 2295)
    - The Bridge of San Luis Rey stage adaptation correspondence and fragments, 1992 (Box 161, Folder 2296)
    - Wilder, Amos Niven condolence letters, 1993–1994 (Box 161, Folder 2297-2298)
    - Hello Dolly correspondence, programs, photocopied itineraries, 1969–1994 (Box 161, Folder 2299)
    - Miscellaneous newspaper and magazine clippings, 1957; undated (Box 161, Folder 2300)
    - Great Lakes Shakespeare Festival season program, 1984 (Box 161, Folder 2301)
    - Theater journal from the Yale School of Drama and the Yale Repertory Theater, 1993 (Box 161, Folder 2302)
  - Troxell, Gilbert correspondence
    - Wilder, Thornton, 1960–1969 (Box 162, Folder 2303-2305)
    - Wilder, Thornton, 1972 (Box 162, Folder 2306-2307)
    - Wilder, Thornton, 1953–1959 (Box 162, Folder 2308-2309)
    - Troxell's correspondence addressed to Isabel, 1960 August (Box 162, Folder 2310)
    - Wilder, Thornton, 1922–1949 (Box 162, Folder 2311-2312)
- Wilder Family Papers, 1832–2013; Series VII
  This series contains photographs and other papers which represent the lives of the Wilder family and their extended relatives. The Wilders have familial connections to the Tappan, Porter, Lewis, and Niven families. Some of these connections are apparent through photographs or the extended genealogical research that family members did into their own lines. Some of the photographs could be identified while others could not be. Also included in this series are the papers of various family members including Amos Tappan Wilder's collection of materials related to his uncle's works, Thornton MacNess Niven's sermons, and materials related to Thornton Wilder's memorial service.
  The series is arranged into the following subseries: Subseries I: Photographs, Subseries II: Scrapbooks, Subseries III: Wilder family materials, Subseries IV: General Wilder family materials, Subseries V: Thornton Wilder correspondence, Subseries VI: Thornton Wilder research files, Subseries VII: Janet Wilder Dakin materials, Subseries VIII: Thornton MacNess Niven sermons, Subseries IX: Isabel Wilder materials removed from books, Subseries X: Thornton Wilder memorial service materials, Subseries XI: Amos Tappan Wilder materials, Subseries XII: Programs saved by Amos Tappan Wilder, Subseries XIII: Amos Tappan Wilder materials, Subseries XIV: Hello Dolly materials and XV: Oversized materials
  - Photographs, 1832–1989
    - Niven and Wilder grandparents photographs, circa 1910-1917 (Box 163, Folder 2313)
      Includes photographs of Charlotte Topliff Porter, Elizabeth Lewis Niven, Thornton MacNess Niven, Amos Lincoln Wilder, and Charlotte Tappan Niven.
    - Wilder family group photographs, 1911–1957 (Box 163, Folder 2314)
    - Wilder, Charlotte photographs, 1908; undated (Box 163, Folder 2315)
    - Wilder, Thornton army photographs, 1946, undated (Box 163, Folder 2316, Box 414 (Broadside))
    - Wilder, Isabel photographs, 1949–1950 (Box 163, Folder 2317-2319)
    - Wilder, Amos Parker photographs, 1908–1915 (Box 163, Folder 2320)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth photographs, 1948-1949 (Box 163, Folder 2321)
      Includes photographs taken by Carl Van Vechtan of The Skin of Our Teeth productions. One production includes Thornton Wilder in his role as Mr. Antrobus and other photographs are of productions which include Carol Stone and Betty Field.
    - Wilder, Isabella Niven photographs, circa 1888-1924 (Box 163, Folder 2322)
    - Our Town photographs, 1938–1946 (Box 163, Folder 2323)
      Photographs from a New York and a London production.
    - Wilder, Amos Niven photographs, 1900–1935 (Box 163, Folder 2324)
    - Dakin, Janet Wilder photographs, 1912–1928 (Box 164 (Oversize), Folder 2325-2326)
    - McCully, Mary Porter and Walker, Fanny, circa 1875 (Box 164 (Oversize), Folder 2327)
    - Wilder, Isabella, Janet, Charlotte, Isabel, and Thornton photograph, 1917 (Box 164 (Oversize), Folder 2328)
      A photograph taken in Berkeley, California.
    - Homes photograph, undated (Box 164 (Oversize), Folder 2329)
      One photograph labeled as the house on Dwight Street in Berkeley where Janet was born in 1910.
    - Niven, Elizabeth Lewis framed drawing, undated (Box 164 (Oversize), Folder 2330)
    - Niven, Thornton MacNess framed daguerreotype, circa 1873 (Box 164 (Oversize), Folder 2331)